<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily manna</title>
    <link>http://steward.emanna.com/calendar.cfm</link>
    <description></description>
    <item>
      <title>emanna for 05/23/2013</title>
      <link>http://steward.emanna.com/todaysemanna.cfm?readingdate=05/23/2013</link>
      <description> 

&lt;!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC &quot;-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN&quot;&gt;

&lt;html&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
	 &lt;title&gt;Today's eManna&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
p {font-family:verdana,arial,helvetica; font-size:13px; color:black; text-align:justify; font-weight:normal}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;http://www.emmanna.com/scripts/gatag.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!-- google analytics tracking code - www.emanna.com --&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
var gaJsHost = ((&quot;https:&quot; == document.location.protocol) ? &quot;https://ssl.&quot; : &quot;http://www.&quot;);
document.write(unescape(&quot;%3Cscript src='&quot; + gaJsHost + &quot;google-analytics.com/ga.js' type='text/javascript'%3E%3C/script%3E&quot;));
&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
try {
var pageTracker = _gat._getTracker(&quot;UA-15630105-1&quot;);
pageTracker._setAllowHash(false);
pageTracker._setDomainName(&quot;.emanna.com&quot;);
pageTracker._setAllowLinker(true);
pageTracker._trackPageview();

var rollupTracker = _gat._getTracker(&quot;UA-12551438-1&quot;);
rollupTracker._setAllowHash(false);
rollupTracker._setDomainName(&quot;.emanna.com&quot;);
rollupTracker._setAllowLinker(true);
rollupTracker._trackPageview(location.host + location.pathname);
} catch(err) {}&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!-- end tracking code --&gt;
&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;images/emanna.gif&quot; width=&quot;179&quot; height=&quot;122&quot; border=&quot;2&quot; align=&quot;absmiddle&quot; alt=&quot;emanna&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			  
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Emanna for 05/23/2013&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			
			 
			 
			 
			 
			 
			   
			 
			   
			  
			 
			 
			 
			 
			
			&lt;p&gt;Cleansing Ten Lepers from Samaria&lt;p&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bible Verses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/b&gt; (RcV)                    &lt;p&gt;Luke 17:11  And as He was going to Jerusalem, He passed  between Samaria and Galilee.  (12) And as He entered into a  certain village, ten leprous men, who stood at a distance,  met Him.  (13) And they raised their voice, saying, Jesus,  Master, have mercy on us!  (14) And when He saw them, He said  to them, Go and show yourselves to the priests. And as they  went, they were cleansed.  (15) And one of them, when he saw  that he was healed, returned, glorifying God with a loud  voice;  (16) And he fell on his face at His feet, thanking  Him. And he was a Samaritan.  (17) And Jesus answered and  said, Were not the ten cleansed? But the nine, where are  they?  (18) Were none found who returned to give glory to God  except this foreigner?  (19) And He said to him, Rise up and  go; your faith has healed you.&lt;p&gt;                   &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Words of Ministry&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/b&gt;                   &lt;p&gt;In 17:11-19 we have the record of the Man-Savior's cleansing  ten lepers in Samaria. Instead of making any selection, the  Lord immediately healed them all. Actually, He did not say to  them, &quot;Be healed!&quot; He said, &quot;Go and show yourselves to the  priests. And it came about as they were going away, they were  cleansed.&quot; Only one of the ten--a Samaritan--remembered the  One who had healed him and came back to say something to Him  (vv. 15-16). The important point is that this record reveals  the highest standard of morality in the Lord's saving grace.&lt;p&gt;We know from chapter ten of the Gospel of Luke that while the  Lord was on the way through Samaria, He was rejected in  Samaria. The Lord must have realized that the majority of the  ten lepers in 17:11-19 were Samaritans. If I had been the  Lord, I might have said, &quot;You Samaritans rejected Me and now  you come to Me for cleansing. You must regret the wrong that  you did to Me and apologize, and then I will heal you.&quot; The  Man-Savior, however, did not calculate matters in this way.  On the contrary, He acted in the highest standard of morality  to exercise His saving grace. As soon as the ten appealed to  Him for mercy, He healed them all without preference. This  displays His high standard of morality in His salvation.&lt;p&gt;                                                        &lt;p&gt;Bible verses are taken from the Recovery Version of the Bible  (RcV) and Words of Ministry from Witness Lee, Life-study of   Luke, pp. 329-330.  Both are published by Living Stream  Ministry, Anaheim, CA.  &lt;p&gt;Please visit us at www.emanna.com Comments to: comment@emanna.com. &lt;/p&gt;
			
			

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 06:00:03 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>