<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily manna</title>
    <link>http://steward.emanna.com/calendar.cfm</link>
    <description></description>
    <item>
      <title>emanna for 07/16/2012</title>
      <link>http://steward.emanna.com/todaysemanna.cfm?readingdate=07/16/2012</link>
      <description> 

&lt;!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC &quot;-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN&quot;&gt;

&lt;html&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
	 &lt;title&gt;Today's eManna&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
p {font-family:verdana,arial,helvetica; font-size:13px; color:black; text-align:justify; font-weight:normal}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;http://www.emmanna.com/scripts/gatag.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!-- google analytics tracking code - www.emanna.com --&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
var gaJsHost = ((&quot;https:&quot; == document.location.protocol) ? &quot;https://ssl.&quot; : &quot;http://www.&quot;);
document.write(unescape(&quot;%3Cscript src='&quot; + gaJsHost + &quot;google-analytics.com/ga.js' type='text/javascript'%3E%3C/script%3E&quot;));
&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
try {
var pageTracker = _gat._getTracker(&quot;UA-15630105-1&quot;);
pageTracker._setAllowHash(false);
pageTracker._setDomainName(&quot;.emanna.com&quot;);
pageTracker._setAllowLinker(true);
pageTracker._trackPageview();

var rollupTracker = _gat._getTracker(&quot;UA-12551438-1&quot;);
rollupTracker._setAllowHash(false);
rollupTracker._setDomainName(&quot;.emanna.com&quot;);
rollupTracker._setAllowLinker(true);
rollupTracker._trackPageview(location.host + location.pathname);
} catch(err) {}&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!-- end tracking code --&gt;
&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;images/emanna.gif&quot; width=&quot;179&quot; height=&quot;122&quot; border=&quot;2&quot; align=&quot;absmiddle&quot; alt=&quot;emanna&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			  
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Emanna for 07/16/2012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			
			 
			 
			 
			 
			 
			   
			 
			   
			  
			 
			 
			 
			 
			
			&lt;p&gt;Deciding that Your Family is for the Lord&lt;p&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bible Verses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/b&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;Joshua 24:15 And if it seems wrong in your sight to serve  Jehovah choose for yourselves today whom you will serve,  either the gods from across the River, whom your fathers  served, or the gods of the Amorites, in whose land you dwell.  But as for me and my house, we will serve Jehovah. (16) And  the people answered and said, far be it from us that we would  forsake Jehovah to serve other gods;&lt;p&gt;                  &lt;b&gt;Words of Ministry&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;                      &lt;p&gt;I would like to speak specifically to the heads of  households. The head of a family has the special  responsibility before God for bringing his whole household to  the Lord and to His service. The head of the household can  decide for his entire household. Even if the little children  do not believe, you can still say that your household will  believe in the Lord, because this household is yours and not  your children's. You are responsible for your household, not  your children. You can declare Joshua 24:15 before the Lord  and before your whole family: &quot;As for me and my house, we  will serve Jehovah.&quot; You have to acknowledge that your family  is a believer's family. &lt;p&gt;Always lay hold of this fact: I am the head of my family, and  my family will believe in God. I have decided that this  family will be a family that worships God. I have decided  that this family will be a family that believes in the Lord.  If you declare this with faith, and if you exercise your  authority to take the lead, your children will go along. The  household is yours, and you have the power to decide whether  this house will serve the Lord. When you take this stand,  everyone who is under you will come to the Lord; they will  have no other way to take. This is marvelous!&lt;p&gt;                                                          &lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bible verses are taken from the Recovery Version of the Bible  and Words of Ministry from Watchman Nee, Messages for  Building Up New Believers, pp. 317-318. Both are published by  Living Stream Ministry, Anaheim, CA&lt;/p&gt;
			
			

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 06:00:04 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>