<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily manna</title>
    <link>http://steward.emanna.com/calendar.cfm</link>
    <description></description>
    <item>
      <title>emanna for 07/23/2012</title>
      <link>http://steward.emanna.com/todaysemanna.cfm?readingdate=07/23/2012</link>
      <description> 

&lt;!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC &quot;-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN&quot;&gt;

&lt;html&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
	 &lt;title&gt;Today's eManna&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
p {font-family:verdana,arial,helvetica; font-size:13px; color:black; text-align:justify; font-weight:normal}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

&lt;body&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;http://www.emmanna.com/scripts/gatag.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!-- google analytics tracking code - www.emanna.com --&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
var gaJsHost = ((&quot;https:&quot; == document.location.protocol) ? &quot;https://ssl.&quot; : &quot;http://www.&quot;);
document.write(unescape(&quot;%3Cscript src='&quot; + gaJsHost + &quot;google-analytics.com/ga.js' type='text/javascript'%3E%3C/script%3E&quot;));
&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
try {
var pageTracker = _gat._getTracker(&quot;UA-15630105-1&quot;);
pageTracker._setAllowHash(false);
pageTracker._setDomainName(&quot;.emanna.com&quot;);
pageTracker._setAllowLinker(true);
pageTracker._trackPageview();

var rollupTracker = _gat._getTracker(&quot;UA-12551438-1&quot;);
rollupTracker._setAllowHash(false);
rollupTracker._setDomainName(&quot;.emanna.com&quot;);
rollupTracker._setAllowLinker(true);
rollupTracker._trackPageview(location.host + location.pathname);
} catch(err) {}&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!-- end tracking code --&gt;
&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;images/emanna.gif&quot; width=&quot;179&quot; height=&quot;122&quot; border=&quot;2&quot; align=&quot;absmiddle&quot; alt=&quot;emanna&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			  
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Emanna for 07/23/2012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			
			 
			 
			 
			 
			 
			   
			 
			   
			  
			 
			 
			 
			 
			
			&lt;p&gt;Christ is the Holy and Faithful Things (2)&lt;p&gt;                      &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bible Verses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/b&gt;                        &lt;p&gt;John 14:6 Jesus said to him, I am the way and the reality and  the life; no one comes to the Father except through Me. 1 Corinthians 1:30 But of Him you are in Christ Jesus, who became  wisdom to us from God: both righteousness and sanctification  and redemption,&lt;p&gt;                     &lt;b&gt;Words of Ministry&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;                          &lt;br&gt; [Part 2 of 2] &lt;br&gt; What are these holy and trustworthy things? They are all the  aspects of what Christ is. According to the New Testament,  Christ is life, light, grace, righteousness, holiness,  sanctification, and justification. He is also the bread of  life and the living water. Furthermore, the holy and  trustworthy things include all the aspects of Christ unveiled  in 1 Corinthians: power, wisdom, righteousness,  sanctification, redemption, glory, the depths of God, the  unique foundation of God's building, the Passover, the  unleavened bread, the spiritual food, the spiritual drink,  the spiritual rock, the Head, the Body, the firstfruit, the  second Man, and the last Adam. We see many more aspects of  Christ in the Gospel of John, such as the Shepherd and the  pasture. Oh, how much Christ is to us as the holy and  trustworthy things! As the resurrected One, He is the  firstborn Son, the Savior, and all the holy and trustworthy  things.&lt;p&gt;In the Old Testament the holy and faithful things are  regarded as mercies. Do you know what mercy is? Mercy implies  both love and grace, but it reaches further than love. Where  love and grace cannot reach, mercy can reach. All the holy  and faithful things are Christ Himself as mercies to us. Life  is mercy, and light is also a mercy. Try to count all the  aspects of these mercies. If you took the time to count them,  you would have a long list of mercies.&lt;p&gt;                                                            &lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bible verses are taken from the Recovery Version of the Bible  and Words of Ministry, from Witness Lee, Life-study of  Acts, p. 323-324. Both are published by Living Stream  Ministry, Anaheim, CA.&lt;/p&gt;
			
			

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 06:00:07 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>